{
    "subject": "resource/Owen_Barfield",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Samuel_Taylor_Coleridge",
    "human_readable": "Owen Barfield was influenced by Samuel Taylor Coleridge.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9401345252990723,
            "question": "Who influenced Owen Barfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8762916922569275,
            "question": "Name a writer who influenced Owen Barfield."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8635372519493103,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Owen Barfield and Samuel Taylor Coleridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8580673336982727,
            "question": "What connection exists between Samuel Taylor Coleridge and Owen Barfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8090382218360901,
            "question": "Who was influential to Owen Barfield's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7890260219573975,
            "question": "Which literary figure is known to have influenced Owen Barfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.772049605846405,
            "question": "What is the name of the writer who influenced Owen Barfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6742977499961853,
            "question": "What literary figure had an impact on Owen Barfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6250881552696228,
            "question": "Who was a source of inspiration for Owen Barfield's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5822403430938721,
            "question": "Can you identify a writer who inspired Owen Barfield?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Owen Barfield was influenced by Samuel Taylor Coleridge.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7979_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was a source of inspiration for Owen Barfield's writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7979_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What literary figure had an impact on Owen Barfield?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7979_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the writer who influenced Owen Barfield?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7979_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7979_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Owen Barfield's poetic philosophy outwits passivity by resituating the subject in a participatory middle, which is shaped most emphatically from Coleridge. Additionally, it is stated that Barfield attempted to wed philosophy and poetry utilizing what he called polar logic, following Samuel Taylor Coleridge. This suggests that Owen Barfield was influenced by Samuel Taylor Coleridge's ideas on philosophy and poetry."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports the statement that Owen Barfield was influenced by Samuel Taylor Coleridge. The documents mention that chapter 2 introduces Coleridge as a significant influence on Barfield's poetic philosophy, and how Barfield adopted Coleridge\u2019s Platonic scheme in his work."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}